Register of the S. I. Hayakawa papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Administrative/Legislative Files (Boxes 1-265)
  - S. 2221 - Amend IRC re net capital gain
  - S. 2224 - Amend. Sm. Bus. Act re solar energy
  - S. 2226 - Amend IRC marriage tax (Box 21)
  - S. 2239 - Amend IRC re income tax treatment of incentive stock option
  - S. 2247 - Small and Rural Laboratory Protection Act
  - S. 2304 - Relief of Alex Mensah Akoto & Grace Owusu Akoto
  - S. 2307 - Harvey's Fishing Hole
  - S. 2325 - Amend Fed. Elect. Campaign Act
  - S. 2360 - Reduce overlap between food stamp & school lunch programs
  - S. 2376 - Food Stamp Accountability Act of, 1980
  - S. 2437 - American Sovereignty Protection Act
  - S. 2521 - Windfall profit tax, equitable treatment of royalty owners
  - S. 2532 - Oil and gas leases
  - S. 2545 - Colorado River Basin Salinity Control Act
  - S. 2547 - Amend IRC re beverage container facilities
  - S. 2580 - Date of birth for naturalized citizens
  - S. 2596 - Educational assistance for service personnel
  - S. 2606 - Office of Strategic Trade
  - S. 2620 - Small Business participation in exporting
  - S. 2523 - Incorporate US Submarine Vets of WWII
  - S. 2641 - Housing & Cty Dev. Act amend.
  - S. 2696 - Ridesharing programs
  - S. 2718 - Exporting
  - S. 2722 - Disability Insurance Benefits
  - S. 2732 - DMSO as a painkiller for arthritis
  - S. 2763 - Foreign Corrupt Practices Act amend.
  - S. 2773 - Establish National Export Policy
  - S. 2791 - Palo Verde Irrigation District Diversion Dam
  - S. 2799 - Amend National School Lunch Act & Child Nutrition Act
  - S. 2835 - Sacramento Valley Canals, Central Valley Project, CA
  - S. 2848 - Royalty Owners Under Windfall Profits
  - S. 2871 - Conveyance of certain lands in Mammoth Lakes
  - S. 2875 - Amend Farm Labor Contractor Registration Act
  - S. 2878 - Permanent Tax Reductions
  - S. 2886 - Amend U.S. Grain Standards Act
  - S. 2890 - Resident status to Soviet Pentacostal in American Embassy, Moscow
  - S. 2899 - Orange Coast National Urban Park
  - S. 2918 - U.S. citizenship to Leopoldine Schmid
  - S. 2924 - Amend Internal Revenue Code re increased investment by individuals (tax rollover)
  - S. 2926 - Engineerig feasibility of magnetic confinement fusion
  - S. 2927 - Interest rate differential
  - S. 2928 - Charter for FBI
  - S. 2929 - Establish intelligence community
  - S. 2981 - Tax incentives for small businesses participating debentures
  - S. 2983 - Tax on capital gains
  - S. 3017 - Water resources developments
  - S. 3030 - Income tax credits re transportation
  - S. 3160 - Debt collection
  - S. 3189 - Peter & Hannah Emilie Pipim
  - S. 3199 - Herman Miller; Congressional Medal of Honor
  - S. 3200 - Periodic inspection & testing of motor vehicles
  - S. 3204 - Election reform/9 PM closing
  - S. 3205 - Election reform/8 PM closing
  - S. 3206 - Election reform/Sunday, 12-9 PM
  - S. 3207 - Election reform/embargo of votes 'til all polls close
  - S. 3227 - Relief of Benjamin Bane
  - S. 3245 - Clinical investigations involving prisoners
  - S. Res. 12 - Continued commitment of US to security of Taiwan
  - S. Res. 13 - Continuing relationship of the US with the Republic of China
  - S. Res. 15 - Concerning Mutual Defense Treaties
  - S. Res. 17 - Relative to death of Rep. Leo J. Ryan of California
  - S. Res. 50 - Saltenstall-Kennedy funds - fishing industry improvement
  - S. Res. 71 - Strong and independent Department of Agriculture
  - S. Res. 83 - Water Policy
  - S. Res. 87 - Allocation of necessary energy sources to the travel & tourism industry
  - S. Res. 99 - War Crimes statute
  - S. Res. 106 - Ambassador to Afghanistan
  - S. Res. 216 - Construction of buildings for the US Senate
  - S. Res. 277 - Human suffering in Cambodia
  - S. Res. 292 - Re release of US personnel in Iran
  - S. Res. 304 - Commending Great Britain on peace in Zimbabwe-Rhodesia
  - S. Res. 315 - American hostages in Iran
  - S. Res. 318 - American hostages in Iran
  - S. Res. 333 - Re summer Olympics in Moscow
  - S. Res. 340 - Regarding Andrei Sakharov
  - S. Res. 344 - Canada & escape of Americans from Iran
  - S. Res. 380 - Limit federal budget outlays to 21% of GNP
  - S. Res. 391 - National Mime Week
  - S. Res. 407 - 2nd Olympic Winter Games for Physically Handicapped
  - S. Res. 411 - Withholding Tax on Certain Interest and Dividends
  - S. Res. 417 - 8 American Servicmen killed in Iranian rescue attempt
  - S. Res. 448 - Select Cte on Indian Affairs made permanent
  - S. Res. 453 - Hostages in Iran & enforcement of Logan Act (Box 22)
  - S. Res. 456 - Logan Act violations
  - S. Res. 461 - EPA grants for waste
  - S. Res. 472 - Withdrawal of Soviet troops from Afghanistan
  - S. Res. 473 - Deploring politicization of Mid-Decade Women's Conference
  - S. Res. 477 - Credit controls
  - S. Res. 484 - Treaty of Mutual Cooperation and Security with Japan
  - S. Res. 503 - Printing compilation of essays
  - S. Res. 562 - Opposition to any attempt by Soviet Union to invade Poland
  - S. Con. Res. 7 - Nonenforcement of sanctions against Zimbabwe-Rhodesia
  - S. Con. Res. 8 - Observers for Rhodesian elections
  - S. Con. Res. 24 - Nonenforcement of sanctions against Zimbabwe-Rhodesia
  - S. Res. 37 - 1980 Olympic Games
  - S. Res. 50 - Urge Soviet Union to allow Ida Nudel to emigrate to Israel
  - S. Con. Res. 52 - Sanctions against Zimbabwe-Rhodesia
  - S. Con. Res. 60 - Treatment of Christians in Soviet Union
  - S. Con. Res. 62 - Allow Irina Astakhova McClellan to emigrate to US from USSR
  - S. Con. Res. 70 - Move Moscow Olympics
  - S. Con. Res. 72 - Thailand & Cambodia
  - S. Con. Res. 73 - International Year of Disabled Persons
  - S. Con. Res. 89 - Overthrow of government of Liberia
  - S. Con. Res. 92 - Congress does not favor withholding income tax on interest and dividends
  - S. Con. Res. 111 - Human rights violations
  - S. Con. Res. 120 - Conclusion of Poland's strike
  - S. Con. Res. 137 - Authorize changes in enrollment of HR 7765
  - S.J. Res. 3 - Termination of any mutual defense treaty
  - S.J. Res. 25 - Limiting terms for Senator and Representatives
  - S.J. Res 31 - Peace, prosperity and welfare of the people of Taiwan
  - S.J. Res. 77 - Congratulating Apollo Program on 10th anniversary of moon landing
  - S.J. Res. 94 - National Mime Week, 1980
  - S.J. Res. 99 - National Lupus Week
  - S.J. Res. 106 - National Mobile Home/Mfc Housing Week
  - S.J. Res. 119 - Vietnam Vets Memorial Fund
  - S.J. Res. 132 - National Medic Alert Week
  - S.J. Res. 142 - Walt Disney
  - S.J. Res. 146 - National Small Business Week
  - S.J. Res. 158 - Iwo Jima reunion
  - S.J. Res. 164 - Relating to Human Rights in Iran
  - S.J. Res. 201 - National Lupus Week
  - S.J. Res. 205 - National Agriculture Day
  - Legislative Activities of S.I. Hayakawa
  - Printed amendments
  - Unprinted amendments
  - S. 1 - Cost of living adjustments in individual tax rates and amount of personal exemptions
  - S. 2 - Amend IR Code of, 1954
  - S. 3 - Amend Davis Bacon Act
  - S. 19 - Royalty owners under crude oil windfall profit tax
  - S. 25 - Educational assistance for vets
  - S. 52 - Periodic inspection & testing of motor vehicles (Box 23)
  - S. 53 - Bilingual ballots requirements
  - S. 54 - Repeal 55 mph speed limit
  - S. 55 - Day & time of for elections of electors for Pres. & V.P.
  - S. 56 - Same as S. 55
  - S. 57-58 - Same as S. 55
  - S. 63 - Compliance date extensions for steel-making facilities on a case-by-case basis, modernization
  - S. 66 - American Sov. Protection Act
  - S. 144 - Export trading companies
  - S. 195 - To incorporate US submarine veterans of WW II
  - S. 232 - Public utility property taxes
  - S. 233 - Congressional Medal of Honor for Herman Miller
  - S. 239 - Income tax credit for purchase of commuter highway vehicle
  - S. 259 - Repeal earnings ceiling of Soc. Sec. Act for benef. 65 & older
  - S. 287 - Capital recovery for investment in plant & equipment
  - S. 304 - Establish national tourism policy
  - S. 312 - Relief of Chmykhalov & Vashcenko families
  - S. 360 - Promote capital investment in small business
  - S. 391 - Secrecy of intelligence relationships and personnel
  - S. 395 - Estate & gift tax equity for family enterprises
  - S. 398 - Ten-hour day w/four-day work week
  - S. 410 - Reform Powerplant and Industrial Fuel Use Act
  - S. 451 - Losses of US agricultural land
  - S. 468 - Health-care benefits for former POWs
  - S. 505 - Improve quality of table grapes for marketing in US
  - S. 506 - Reinstate and validate US oil and gas leases
  - S. 509 - Delete req. for support price of milk adjusted semiannually
  - S. 521 - Relief of Benjamin Bane
  - S. 522 - Create new CA Pacific Council with authority over fisheries in Pacific Ocean
  - S. 539 - Prohibit use of fund for 9 digit zip code
  - S. 569 - Investment tax credit for soil & water conservation expenditures
  - S. 580 - Establish program levels for SBA Polution Control Bond Program
  - S. 591 - Debt collection for debts owed the US
  - S. 599 - Amend IRC of to provide for a definition of "artificial bait", 1954
  - S. 657 - Herbert Clark Hoover Department of Commerce Building
  - S. 682 - Moratorium on decisions of FTC re shared monopoly proc.
  - S. 683 - Reduce tax rates for indiv. & accel. of capital cost recovery for plant equip. & real property
  - S. 700 - Re Fed royalties from WFP tax
  - S. 708 - Amend & clarify Foreign Corrupt Practices Act
  - S. 734 - Export Trading Companies
  - S. 736 - Provide control of illegally taken fish and wildlife
  - S. 753 - Exemp. of state and local govts & windfall profit tax
  - S. 842 - To provide for stability and certainty in planning and management of certain National Forest lands
  - S. 875 - Auth. the gen. of elec. power at Palo Verde Irr. Dis. Div. Dam, Calif.
  - S. 881 - Small business innovation
  - S. 883 - Redbank and Fancher Creeks improvements
  - S. 890 - Improve procedures for issuance of agency rules
  - S. 922 - Amend Farm Labor Contractor Reg. Act of, 1963
  - S. 930 - Guest Worker Act of, 1981
  - S. 940 - Donation of historical film & tax deductions
  - S. 941 - Draza Mihailovich monument
  - S. 1018 - Protect & conserve fish and wildlife (Box 24)
  - S. 1030 - Protect firearms owners const. rights & civil liberties
  - S. 1080 - Improve effectiveness and decr. compliance cost-govts
  - S. 1117 - Mt. Shasta Wilderness
  - S. 1131 - Interest on overdue payments & discounts on early payments
  - S. 1230 - LA commemorative Olympic coin
  - S. 1242 - El Dorado National Forest
  - S. 1245 - Cession and conveyance of federal land to states
  - S. 1249 - Collection of debts owed US
  - S. 1277 - Regulation of vitamin and mineral products
  - S. 1278 - Saccharin Study & Labelling Act Amendment of, 1981
  - S. 1310 - Tax incentives in depressed areas
  - S. 1329 - Relief of Samuel Joseph Edgar
  - S. 1330 - Relief of Jose Garcia-Nunez and Maura Garcia-Nunez
  - S. 1331 - Relief of Florence Louis Barry
  - S. 1347 - Credit agst tax for employment of members of targeted groups
  - S. 1363 - Saccharin Study and Labelling Act
  - S. 1389 - Deep-draft commercial ports
  - S. 1412 - Travel expenses of State legislators
  - S. 1414 - Clear title to land on CA-Nev border
  - S. 1422 - Donation of surplus property to states
  - S. 1424 - Investment Company Act of, 1940
  - S. 1442 - Food Safety regulations
  - S. 1448 - Girl Scout 70th anniversary postage stamp
  - S. 1504 - Provide greater protection against plant pests
  - S. 1506 - Same as S. 1504
  - S. 1550 - Compulsory union dues - use for political purposes
  - S. 1581 - Choice of tax credit or deduction for dependent 65 years or older
  - S. 1616 - Floraboard
  - S. 1657 - Uniform Science and Tech Research and Development Utilization Act
  - S. 1676 - Motor Vehicle Theft
  - S. 1697 - Delay price support increase for milk, etc.
  - S. 1698 - Preferential treatment to certain children of US Armed Forces Personnel
  - S. 1701 - Identification of deceased indiv. & in location of missing children
  - S. 1748 - Fixed contribution multi-employer pension plans
  - S. 1782 - Contract progress payments made by agencies
  - S. 1803 - Relief of Dick Shan Ng
  - S. 1814 - Req. Secy to comply w/court orders re uniformed service
  - S. 1867 - Reclamation law
  - S. 1947 - Improve sm. bus. access to Fed. procurement information
  - S. 1951 - Penalties for possession of contrld. substances
  - S. 1958 - Coverage of hospice care under Medicare
  - S. 2002 - Bilingual education
  - S. 2020 - Individual income tax rate reductions
  - S. 2005 - Relief of Vottoria Givone
  - S. 2061 - Conservation, rehabilitation, and improvement of national and cultural resources
  - S. 2101 - Relief of Jacquelin Ann Kaufman
  - S. 2125 - Relief of Crescencio Antonia Folgar
  - S. 2126 - Relief of Oscar Renetiz
  - S. 2130 - Development of drugs for rare diseases and conditions
  - S. 2174 - Recog. organ. of American Ex-Prisoners of War
  - S. 2191 - Relief of In Hon Song & Sung J. Park
  - S. 2199 - Coops participation in DISCs
  - S. 2202 - Amend Colorado River Basin Salinity Control Act
  - S. 2226 - Emergency interest reduction payments - housing
  - S. 2278 - Promoting public sector proc. of goods & svcs from profit making business concerns
  - S. 2298 - Enterprise Zone Tax Act of, 1982
  - S. 2309 - Auth. funds for Endangered Species
  - S. 2393 - Amend Legal Services Corp Act
  - S. 2412 - Bilingual education
  - S. 2418 - Lease of land to Indians
  - S. 2420 - Protect victims of crime
  - S. 2446 - Procurement for small businesses (Box 25)
  - S. 2480 - Amend Food Stamp Act
  - S. 2507 - Warrant for entrance to ag operation
  - S. 2514 - Removal of OASI, DI, HI trust funds from Soc. Sec.
  - S. 2522 - Amend food stamp act of, 1977
  - S. 2572 - Strengthen law enforcement in area of violent crime & drug enforcement
  - S. 2620-2621 - FIFRA
  - S. 2632 - Bonds to American Samoa
  - S. 2684 - Construct, operate and maintain the Santa Margarita Project
  - S. 2741 - Excess business holdings prov. to private foundations
  - S. 2742 - Capitol Page Board
  - S. 2750 - Relief of You-xing Zhou Ling
  - S. 2773 - To amend Export Admin. Act of, 1979
  - S. 2792 - Ocean and Coastal Develop. Impact Assist. Fund
  - S. 2808 - Trinity River
  - S. 2811 - Tuolumne River
  - S. 2822 - Academic Standards for Assistance Under Higher Ed. Act
  - S. 2855 - Amend Federal Seed Act re lawn and turf
  - S. 2907 - Relief of Hisato Diozake
  - S. 2909 - Financial Assistance for Continuing Ed. Programs
  - S. 3060 - Amend Wild & Scenic Rivers Act
  - SCRes 4 - Int'l Year of Disabled Persons
  - SCRes 5 - Imprisonment & treatment of Dr. Viktor Bailovsky by USSR
  - SCRes 9 - Revise Cong. Budget for US for FY, 1981, 2 & 3
  - SCRes 10 - Express sense of Senate re continue permanent conversion productive ag lands to non ag uses
  - SCRes 12 - re Reagan's Economic Recovery Proposals
  - SCRes 15 - Grain embargo to USSR
  - SCRes 21 - Sense of Cong re Baltic States question
  - SCRes 29 - Disapproving certain Coastal Zone Mgmt Fed. Consist. Regula.
  - SCRes 46 - Mutual security efforts of US and Japan
  - SCRes 47 - Imprisonment of Alexander Paritsky & family
  - SCRes 53 - Policies of USSR re anti-Semitism
  - SCRes 69 - Ida Nudel
  - SCRes 73 - Condemn Iranian persecution of Bahai community
  - SCRes 76 - Express sense of Cong re families seeking refuge in US Embassy in Moscow
  - SCRes 84 - Centennial of establishment of diplomatic relations between US & Korea
  - SCRes 90 - Declaration of UN of Int'l Year Against Drug Abuse
  - SCRes 98 - Thailand's bicentennial
  - SCRes 114 - Space Shuttle
  - SCRes 126 - Material assistance to Afghanistan
  - SCRes 131 - Missing & unaccounted for in Southeast Asia
  - SCRes 133 - National security policy of US
  - SJRes 25 - Const. amendment limiting number of terms for Senators & Congressmen
  - SJRes 28 - Women's History Week
  - SJRes 40 - National Recognition Day for Vets of Vietnam era
  - SRJes 42 - National Ministers Day
  - SJRes 47 - National Small Business Week
  - SJRes 58 - Jt. res. proposing amnd. to Const. altering Fed. fiscal dec.-making proced.
  - SJRes 60 - Autho. & req. the Pres. to des. the week as "National Physical Fitness & Sports Week", May 3-9, 1981
  - SJRes 61 - African Refugee Relief Day
  - SJRes 65 - Making Raoul Wallenberg an honorary US citizen
  - SJRes 72 - Const. amend re English as official language
  - SJRes 73 - Management Week in America
  - SJRes 80 - U.S.O. Week
  - SJRes 91 - National Peach Week
  - SJRes 92 - Older Americans Employment Opportunity Week
  - SJRes 93 - Clarify govt use of private enterprise system
  - SJRes 103 - National Port Week
  - SJRes 114 - Hungarian Freedom Day
  - SJRes 123 - National Disabled Veterans Week, 1982
  - SJRes 124 - Playing of taps at Vietnam Vets Memorial
  - SJRes 131 - National Theatre Week
  - SJRes 141 - National Crime Prevention Week
  - SJRes 142 - Afghanistan Day
  - SJRes 143 - National Physical Fitness and Sports for all Week, 1982
  - SJRes 148 - National Agriculture Day (Box 26)
  - SJRes 153 - Baltic Freedom Day
  - SJRes 158 - Policy of US re Cuba
  - SJRes 159 - White House Conference on Aging
  - SJRes 160 - POW/MIA Recognition Day
  - SJRes 177 - Reduction of nuclear weapons by US & USSR
  - SJRes 180 - National Small Business Week
  - SJRes 181 - Jewish Heritage Week
  - SJRes 184 - Native American Day
  - SJRes 201 - Baltic Freedom Day
  - SJRes 202 - Expeditious development of magnetic fusion energy
  - SJRes 207 - National Purple Heart Week
  - SJRes 209 - National Adult Day Care Center Week
  - SJRes 213 - ERA
  - SJRes 215 - Woman's History Week
  - SJRes 227 - National Firefighters Week
  - SJRes 232 - National Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Awareness Week
  - SJRes 233 - National Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Awareness Week
  - SJRes 235 - National Agriculture Day, (1983)
  - SJRes 236 - National Water Resources Week
  - SJRes 239 - National Newspaper Carrier Appreciation Day
  - SJRes 241 - National Drunk & Drugged Driving Awareness Week
  - SJRes 258 - National Close-Captioned Televison Month
  - SJRes 264 - National Children & Television Week
  - SJRes 265 - National Year of Voluntarism
  - SRes 21 - Commending James duMaresq Clavell for contributions to literature
  - SRes 28 - Release of American hostages held captive in Iran
  - SRes 98 - American History Month
  - SRes 100 - Honor Joseph Rosenthal photographer
  - SRes 101 - Change stat. of commm. on small bus. to a stand. comm. & other purposes
  - SRes 106 - Com. Agts. McCarthy & Parr & Off. Delahanty; courage, patriotism re saving Reagan
  - SRes 115 - Collision of US submarine & Japanese freighter
  - SRes 116 - Merger between Texas Intl Airlines & Continental Airlines
  - SRes 131 - Imprisonment of Anatoly Shcharansky
  - SRes 133 - Concern over attack on Pope John Paul II
  - SRes 138 - Solidarity Sunday
  - SRes 139 - Access of farmer-owned refining businesses to crude oil at reasonable prices
  - SRes 155 - 50th anniversary of Radio City Music Hall
  - SRes 161 - Impact Aid
  - SRes 167 - Commending disabled indiv. who climbed Mt. Rainier
  - SRes 198 - Release of Benedict Scott
  - SRes 199 - National Productivity Improvement Week
  - SRes 220 - Food Crisis in Poland
  - SRes 221 - Sale of Defense Articles to Saudi Arabia
  - SRes 232 - Tax incentives re energy conserv. & sources
  - SRes 299 - International Franchise Day
  - SRes 330 - Imposition of martial law in Poland & release of L. Walesa
  - SRes 335 - Death of Hon. Clifford P. Case
  - SRes 337 - Invest. & report by Rules Cte re ABSCAM-type procedures
  - SRes 338 - Invest by standing or select cte re ABSCAM-type procedures
  - SRes 355 - Fed. fund for energy conserv. and renewable energy
  - SRes 381 - Solidarity Sunday
  - SRes 442 - Georgia Day
  - SRes 451 - Asylum for Hu Na
  - SRes 453 - National Productivity Improvement Week
  - SRes 500 - Commending govt of Zimbabwe
  - SRes 501 - Solidarity w/Poland
  - Agriculture
    - Western State Conservation Act of 1977, 8/3/77
    - Article on Undocumented Aliens, 1/30/80
    - S. 2376, Food Stamp Accountability Act, 3/4/80
    - Food Stamp Conference Report, 5/14/80
    - Reclamation Editorial, 6/12/80
    - Mechanically Deboned Meat, 8/1/80
    - Walnut and Olive Legislation, 10/2/80
    - Ag. Approp., $500,000 for germ plasm, 11/25/80
    - U.S. Grain Embargo to Soviet Union, 2/5/81
    - S. 505, amends Agriculture Marketing Act of 1937 to include grapes, 2/19/81
    - Immigration Law Reform, 3/2/81
    - "Farmers, We Salute You,", 3/19/81
    - S. 509, casein statement, 3/24/81
    - Introduction of John B. Crowell, Asst. Secy. of Ag. for Nat. Res., 5/19/81
    - H.R. 3991, Cash-out program, Food Stamp Program, 6/25/81
    - S. 1506, Medfly, 7/20/81
    - S. 1616, "Floral Research and Consumer Information Act,", 9/11/81
    - H.R. 4416, Eradication of plant pests and contagious or infectious animal and poultry diseases, 9/11/81
    - S. 884, the Farm Bill, Elimination of peanut acreage allotments, 9/16/81
    - S. 884, the Farm Bill, Floraboard amendment, 9/17/81
    - Amendment to give Secy. of Ag. the authority to take action in infestations such as Medfly in CA, 9/17/81
    - S. 884, the Farm Bill, sugar price supports, 9/17/81
    - S. 884, the Farm Bill, Elimination of Target Prices, 9/18/81
    - S. 884, the Farm Bill, Ag. Export Credit Revolving Fund
    - - Wine: In Quality and Quantity California Leads the Way for the USA, 9/30/81 (Box 27)
    - - Conference Committee on Farm Bill, 12/10/81
    - - Marking Orders, 3/2/82
    - - Malnutrition, 3/11/82
    - - In Celebration of American Agriculture, 3/18/82
    - - S. 2507, requiring warrants to enter farm fields, 5/6/82
    - - Amend the Food Stamp Act of 1977, 5/12/82
    - - S. 2621, FIFRA, 6/10/82
    - - Amnesty is no solution to illegal aliens, 6/17/82
    - - S. 1867, Reclamation, 7/15/82
    - - S. 2774, milk price supports amendment, 8/5/82
    - - S. 2222, Guestworker program amendment, 8/13/82
    - - S. 2222, Immigration bill, 8/13/82
    - - S. 2222, Immigration Reform and Control Act, 8/17/82
    - - S. 2855, Federal Seed Act amendment, 8/18/82
    - - Public Lands to Outlaws (marijuana), 9/22/82
    - - Marijuana cultivation in the US, 9/23/82
    - - Ag. Appropriations, FY 1983, 9/28/82
    - - S. 505, table grapes, 9/29/82
    - - Marijuana cultivation, 9/30/82
    - - Food stamps and Jesse Helms, 10/1/82
    - - Marijuana farmers, 12/3/82
    - - Immigration ignorance, 12/16/82
    - - Welfare Programs, 12/16/82
  - Banking
    - - Credit controls, 3/25/80
    - - Ineffectiveness of credit controls, 6/30/80
    - - Cash Discount Act, 3/12/81
    - - LA Olympic Commemorative Coins, 5/20/81
    - - National Consumer Cooperative Bank, 5/21/81
    - - S. 1424, high yield mutual funds, 6/24/81
    - - Fidelity Savings & Loan vs. De La Cuesta, 7/22/82
  - Budget
    - - Budget, 5/4/77
    - - Revenue figure adjustment in budget, 9/9/77
    - - Budget, 4/25/78
    - - Response to President Carter's budget, 1/30/80
    - - S. Res. 380 Budget - limit federal spending, 3/25/80
    - - Alternative to budget resolution, 5/6/80
    - - Comments regarding budget resolution, 5/12/80
    - - H.J. Res. 610, Omnibus Budget Resolution, 9/29/80
    - - S. Con. Res. 448, against budget, 11/19/80
    - - S. Con. Res. 9 - Budget Reconciliation Resolution, 3/25/81
    - - Extension of debt limit, 9/28/81
    - - H.J. Res. 368, temporary continuing resolution, 11/23/81
    - - S.J. Res. 58, Balanced budget, 8/3/82
    - - SIH questions Sen. East during filibuster on cont. res., 12/18/82
  - Commerce, Science, Sports
    - - S. Con. Res. 68, moving 1980 Olympics, 1/24/80
    - - H.C. Res. 249, moving 1980 Olympics, 1/28/80
    - - S. 598, bottling bill, 5/17/80
    - - H.R. 2313, FTC Conference Report, 5/21/80
    - - Space Week, 1980, 6/27/80